[
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who played the role of Harry Potter in the movie series of Harry Potter?",
        "correct_answer": "Daniel Radcliffe",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Holland", "Tom cruise", "Daniel Day-Lewis"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who wrote the book - 'The Hunger Games'",
        "correct_answer": "Suzanne Collins",
        "incorrect_answers": ["JK Rowling", "Toni Morrison", "James Patterson"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the symbol of distance?",
        "correct_answer": "S",
        "incorrect_answers": ["D", "I", "T"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In which Indian state does the river Ganga NOT flow in?",
        "correct_answer": "Maharashtra",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Bihar", "Chhattisgarh", "Uttar Pradesh"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who played the role of Ravi in the 1982 bollywood film, Satte pe Satta?",
        "correct_answer": "Amitabh Bachchan",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Shakti Kapoor", "Amjad Khan", "Sanjeev Kumar"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who played the role of Kabir in the 2019 bollywood film, War?",
        "correct_answer": "Hrithik Roshan",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Tiger Shroff",
            "Abhishekh Bachchan",
            "Shah Rukh Khan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which singer sung the bollywood song, Khairiyat?",
        "correct_answer": "Arijit Singh",
        "incorrect_answers": ["AR Rahman", "Tony Kakkar", "Tushar Joshi"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which film is the highest grossing film, AS OF 2019?",
        "correct_answer": "Avengers: Endgame",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Avatar", "Frozen", "Black Panther"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is a speculative structure linking disparate points in spacetime?",
        "correct_answer": "Wormholes",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Supernova", "Black Hole", "Galaxy"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the symbol of Mercury?",
        "correct_answer": "Hg",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Fe", "Me", "Mr"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who is the mother of Sati (wife of Lord Shiva) in the Hindu mythology?",
        "correct_answer": "Daksha Prajapati",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sita", "Kubera", "Himavan"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of these is not a social media platform?",
        "correct_answer": "Chrome",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Facbook", "Twitter", "Instagram"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of these is a statically typed language?",
        "correct_answer": "TypeScript",
        "incorrect_answers": ["JavaScript", "Python", "Lua"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How many elements exist?",
        "correct_answer": "118",
        "incorrect_answers": ["100", "209", "187"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How many elements exist?",
        "correct_answer": "118",
        "incorrect_answers": ["100", "209", "187"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In which year did Mahatma Gandhi go to South Africa?",
        "correct_answer": "1893",
        "incorrect_answers": ["1901", "1919", "1894"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In which year did Mahatma Gandhi go to South Africa?",
        "correct_answer": "1893",
        "incorrect_answers": ["1901", "1919", "1894"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In which year was Bhagat Singh hanged?",
        "correct_answer": "1931",
        "incorrect_answers": ["1930", "1932", "1940"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who did Alauddin Khalji kill to become the Sultan of the Delhi Sultanate?",
        "correct_answer": "Jalaluddin Firuz Khalji",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Shamsuddin Khalji",
            "Qutb ad-Din Mubarak",
            "Shihab ad-Din Umar"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who played the lead role in the bollywood film, Gabbar is Back?",
        "correct_answer": "Akshay Kumar",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Amitabh Bachchan",
            "Salman Khan",
            "Ranveer Singh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who wrote the Gitanjali?",
        "correct_answer": "Rabindranath Tagore",
        "incorrect_answers": ["R.K. Narayan", "Sri Aurobindo", "Sarojini Naidu"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the 'Hello' in Hindi?",
        "correct_answer": "Namaste",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Shukriya", "Dhanyavad", "Alvida"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the longest waterfall on Earth?",
        "correct_answer": "Angel Falls",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Hero Falls", "High Falls", "Tugela Falls"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who killed Duryodhan in the Mahabharat?",
        "correct_answer": "Bhim",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Arjun", "Yudhishthir", "Nakula"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which company made the coding languages, Dart, Golang and Kotlin?",
        "correct_answer": "Google",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Apple", "Microsoft", "Facebook"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a member of the vitamin B complex?",
        "correct_answer": "Ascorbic acid",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Thiamine", "Riboflavin", "Folic acid"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the these is an air-borne disease?",
        "correct_answer": "Measles",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Typhoid", "Pink eye", "None"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following pair is not a father-son pair?",
        "correct_answer": "Akbar-Aurangzeb",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Babur-Humayun",
            "Akbar-Jahangir",
            "Jahangir-Shah Jahan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who is the female singer in the song, Lovely?",
        "correct_answer": "Billie Eilish",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Selena Gomez", "Lady Gaga", "Shania Twain"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "How many ragas are there in indian classical music?",
        "correct_answer": "83",
        "incorrect_answers": ["93", "84", "87"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which film is the highest grossing Indian film with a worldwide gross of almost â‚¹2,024 crore?",
        "correct_answer": "Dangal",
        "incorrect_answers": ["PK", "3 idiots", "Krrish 3"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following bone is the longest bone in the human body?",
        "correct_answer": "Femur",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Fibula", "Spinal Cord", "Skin"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In which yuga did the Ramayan take place in, in the Hindu Mythology??",
        "correct_answer": "Treta",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Dwapar", "Kalyug", "Balyug"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who put Shah Jahan in prison?",
        "correct_answer": "Aurangazeb",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Shivaji", "Akbar", "Rana Sanga"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following planets is NOT a dwarf planet?",
        "correct_answer": "Kepler-452b",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Eris", "Pluto", "Ceres"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which country reached Mars at its first attempt?",
        "correct_answer": "India",
        "incorrect_answers": ["USA", "Russia", "China"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "How much percent of the total mass of the Solar System does the Sun take?",
        "correct_answer": "99.86%",
        "incorrect_answers": ["99.9%", "97.56%", "99.89%"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "River Hooghly located in West Bengal, India is a tributary of which river?",
        "correct_answer": "Ganga",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Narmada", "Godavari", "Kaveri"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "River Hooghly located in West Bengal, India is a tributary of which river?",
        "correct_answer": "Ganga",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Narmada", "Godavari", "Kaveri"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In which place was Jesus Christ born?",
        "correct_answer": "Bethlehem",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Nazureth", "Constantinople", "Mecca"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which mughal ruler was known as an â€˜engineer kingâ€™?",
        "correct_answer": "Shah Jahan",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Akbar", "Babur", "Jahangir"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What was the old name of Istanbul?",
        "correct_answer": "Constantinople",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Mecca", "Kabul", "Constantinoble"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In which year did Microsoft acquire Minecraft?",
        "correct_answer": "2014",
        "incorrect_answers": ["2013", "2012", "2015"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Whose empire was the largest empire in the histort of the world at some point of time?",
        "correct_answer": "Genghis Khan",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Alexander", "Constantine", "Ashoka"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which song is the most liked youtube video?",
        "correct_answer": "Despacito",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Baby Shark", "Lovely", "Alone"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In which year did Iron Man and Captain America go to after failing once to get the Tessaract in 2014 in Avengers: Endgame??",
        "correct_answer": "1970",
        "incorrect_answers": ["1980", "1990", "1960"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the name of Janet and Peter's dog in the book series, Secret Seven?",
        "correct_answer": "Scamper",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Milo", "Tiger", "Loki"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "If there are 32 men, 34 women and 58 children in a town, and all adults can buy a movie disc 3 times, how many movie disks can be sold?",
        "correct_answer": "198",
        "incorrect_answers": ["200", "201", "197"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who wrote Akbarnama?",
        "correct_answer": "Abu'l-Fazl ibn Mubarak",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Akbar",
            "Ali'l-Hazl ibn Fazeel",
            "Sara'ibn-Hure Muhammad"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the name of the world's first nuclear submarine?",
        "correct_answer": "Nautilus",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Cuttlefish", "Bonita", "Seawolf"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Fill in the blank: 81 is the square of ______",
        "correct_answer": "9",
        "incorrect_answers": ["11", "41", "8"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of the following country does India not share an international border with?",
        "correct_answer": "Sri Lanka",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Pakistan", "Bangladesh", "Nepal"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which country among these does not have an animal on its flag?",
        "correct_answer": "Tuvalu",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Moldova", "Poland", "Zambia"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which statue is the tallest statue in the world?",
        "correct_answer": "Statue of Unity",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Statue of Liberty",
            "Statue of Gautama Buddha",
            "Christ the Redeemer"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In which of the following Harry Potter book did Dobby not make an appearance?",
        "correct_answer": "Prisoner of Askaban",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Deathly Hallows",
            "Chamber of Secrets",
            "Goblet of Fire"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In the game, Minecraft, which picaxe mines the fastest?",
        "correct_answer": "Gold Picaxe",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Dimaond Picaxe",
            "Netherite Picaxe",
            "Iron Picaxe"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who killed Dronacharya in the Mahabharat?",
        "correct_answer": "Dhristadyumna",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ashwathama", "Bhishma", "Arjun"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In the bollywood film Tiger Zinda Hai, how many Indian nurses were kidnapped?",
        "correct_answer": "25",
        "incorrect_answers": ["15", "20", "30"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following elements doesn't have the valency 3?",
        "correct_answer": "Oxygen",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Nitrogen", "Boron", "Carbon"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which organ is the largest organ in the human body?",
        "correct_answer": "Skin",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Small Intestine", "Liver", "Lungs"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Find 'x' - x/2 + 34 = 742",
        "correct_answer": "1416",
        "incorrect_answers": ["742", "1002", "1415"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which IPL cricket team was the first to win 100 matches?",
        "correct_answer": "Mumbai Indians",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Chennai Super Kings",
            "Kolkata Knight Riders",
            "Sunrisers Hyderabad"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following songs isn't sung by Sonu Nigam?",
        "correct_answer": "Lahore",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Bhagwan hai kahan re tuh",
            "Jaane nahi denge tujhe",
            "God Allah aur Bhagwan"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the beat called in Indian classical music?",
        "correct_answer": "Taal",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Raag", "Ragam", "Gavind"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which musical instrument does Zakir Hussain play?",
        "correct_answer": "Tabla",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sitar", "Harmonium", "Harmonica"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The Lion King' is a movie loosely inspired by which of Shakespeare's dramas?",
        "correct_answer": "Hamlet",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Macbeth",
            "Merchant of Venice",
            "Romeo and Juliet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "How many times was J K Rowling's pitch for 'Harry Potter' rejected by publishers?",
        "correct_answer": "12",
        "incorrect_answers": ["10", "0", "11"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "When was Stephen King born?",
        "correct_answer": "21st September",
        "incorrect_answers": ["16th July", "14th May", "10th December"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In which year did the first Harry Potter book release?",
        "correct_answer": "2001",
        "incorrect_answers": ["2000", "1999", "2003"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who played the role of Edward Cullen in 'The Twilight Saga'?",
        "correct_answer": "Robert Pattinson.",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Tom Pattinson",
            "Romeon Patt",
            "Robert Patternson"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who wrote the Panchanchantra?",
        "correct_answer": "Vishnu Sharma",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Kalidasa", "Rabindranath Tagore", "Aryan Sen"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of the following is not a code-editor?",
        "correct_answer": "Electron",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Visual Studio Code", "PyCharm", "Sublime Text"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Father of Computing'?",
        "correct_answer": "Charles Babbage",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Bill Gates", "Ada Lovelace", "Blaise Pascal"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following names is NOT an Android OS name?",
        "correct_answer": "Biscuit",
        "incorrect_answers": ["KitKat", "Lollipop", "Donut"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who is the CEO of Apple as of 2021?",
        "correct_answer": "Tim Cook",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Jobs", "Larry Page", "Sundar Pichai"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "If you were coding by only writing 1 and 0, what are you coding?",
        "correct_answer": "Binary",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Java", "Lua", "Python"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of the following is not made by Facebook?",
        "correct_answer": "Flutter",
        "incorrect_answers": ["React.js", "PyTorch", "React Native"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What does Google not provide in the following?",
        "correct_answer": "Bixby Assisstant",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Glass OS", "reCAPTCHA", "Chromecast"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who gave Bishma the boon that he would die only when he wishes?",
        "correct_answer": "Shantanu",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Dushala", "Krishna", "Ganga"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who gave Bishma the boon that he would die only when he wishes?",
        "correct_answer": "Shantanu",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Dushala", "Krishna", "Ganga"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who vowed to kill Bishma in her next birth?",
        "correct_answer": "Amba",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ambika", "Ambaalika", "Indradev"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which international border is the longest?",
        "correct_answer": "United States-Canada",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "India-Pakistan",
            "China-Russia",
            "Argentina-Brazil"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who is the first Indian individual athlete to win a gold medal in the Olympics?",
        "correct_answer": "Abhinav Bindra",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Dhyan Chand", "Neeraj Chopra", "Kapil Dev"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the meaning of the muhavra - 'Aakash Chuna'",
        "correct_answer": "Bahut Tarakki Karna",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mar jana",
            "Kisiki madad karna",
            "Havaijahas mein urna"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which account is the most followed account on Instagram?",
        "correct_answer": "Instagram",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Lionel Messi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "If a boy is 'angootha chap' then what is he?",
        "correct_answer": "Illiterate",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Brainless", "Without thumb", "Successful"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What are the words that follow the line that comes under the 'MINECRAFT' title in the homescreen of the Minecraft Game? - 'Sodium...'",
        "correct_answer": "Free",
        "incorrect_answers": ["is life", "KEMISTRY", "is love"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which company acquired the game 'Minecraft'?",
        "correct_answer": "Microsoft",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Mojang", "Reliance", "Mineees"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of the following games can't be played online?",
        "correct_answer": "Hill Climb Racing",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Pubg", "Minecraft", "Roblox"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which game is the highest grossing game in the world as of 2021?",
        "correct_answer": "Minecraft",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Roblox", "Pokemon GO", "Pac-man"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is Roblox's previous name?",
        "correct_answer": "DynaBlox",
        "incorrect_answers": ["I_suck", "DinaBlox", "DoodooBloox"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of the following expressions has the lowest value?",
        "correct_answer": "1^0",
        "incorrect_answers": ["4/2", "2^2", "4*4"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Is zero negative or positive?",
        "correct_answer": "Neither",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Negative", "Positive", "Both"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who is known as the father of Algebra?",
        "correct_answer": "Muhammad ibn Musa al-Khwarizmi",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Aryabhatta", "William Jones", "Albert Einstein"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the value of cos 360 degree?",
        "correct_answer": "1",
        "incorrect_answers": ["180", "360", "-360"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who is known as the father of Trigonometry?",
        "correct_answer": "Hipparchus",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Aryabhatta", "Albert Einstein", "John Williams"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "How many zeros are there in a billion?",
        "correct_answer": "9",
        "incorrect_answers": ["8", "7", "10"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who discovered the number line?",
        "correct_answer": "John Walls",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "John Williams",
            "Sara'ibn-Hure Muhammad",
            "Albert Einstein"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which of these prime ministers have never been the chief minister of any Indian state?",
        "correct_answer": "Lal Bahadur Shastri",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Narendra Modi",
            "Indira Ghandhi",
            "Lal Bahadur Modi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The minimum age to qualify for election to the Lok Sabha is?",
        "correct_answer": "25 years",
        "incorrect_answers": ["20 years", "18 years", "30 years"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The Muslim League as a political party was founded in .. ?",
        "correct_answer": "1906",
        "incorrect_answers": ["1909", "1915", "1947"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who was the chief minister of Mahrashtra during the 26/11 Mumbai terrorist attack?",
        "correct_answer": "Vilasrao Deshmukh",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Narendra Modi",
            "Uddhav Thackeray",
            "Devendra Gangadharrao Fadnavis"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who is the 40th president of the United States?",
        "correct_answer": "Ronald Reagan",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Barack Obama", "Joe Biden", "Donald Trump"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who is the prime minister of India as of 2019?",
        "correct_answer": "Narendra Modi",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Manmohan Singh",
            "Mamta Banerjee",
            "Narendra Mori"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What does the Indian Constitution's preamble not contain among these?",
        "correct_answer": "Adult Franchise",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Equality", "Fraternity", "Justice"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the minimum age to become the Prime Minister of India?",
        "correct_answer": "25 years",
        "incorrect_answers": ["20 years", "30 years", "40 years"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "The office of the prime minister of India....",
        "correct_answer": "is created by the constitution",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "rests on coronation",
            "is created by the Parliament",
            "is created by the people of India"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "For how many years are the members of the state legislative elected for?",
        "correct_answer": "5 years",
        "incorrect_answers": ["10 years", "4 years", "No limit"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "How much would you rate this app?",
        "correct_answer": "10/10",
        "incorrect_answers": ["5/10", "0/10", "9/10"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Complete the words that the commentator said when M.S. Dhoni hit the last six in the 2011 World Cup Finals - 'Dhoni finishes off in ...'",
        "correct_answer": "style",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "a high six",
            "making everyone happy",
            "party starts in the room"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who was the captain of India when India won the T20 World Cup in 2007?",
        "correct_answer": "M.S. Dhoni",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sachin Tendulkar", "Virat Kohli", "Yuvraj Singh"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which footballer has scored the most number of goals in international football as of 2021?",
        "correct_answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Pele", "Lionel Messi", "Maradona"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the jersey number of the hockey player Manpreet Singh?",
        "correct_answer": "7",
        "incorrect_answers": ["10", "19", "4"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who won the 2020-21 Indian Super League?",
        "correct_answer": "Mumbai City",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Mohun Bagan", "East Bengal", "Kerala Blasters"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the national sport of India?",
        "correct_answer": "None",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Hockey", "Cricket", "Kabaddi"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which famous Indian cricketer is also known as 'Thala'?",
        "correct_answer": "M.S. Dhoni",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Sachin Tendulkar",
            "Virat Kohli",
            "Harbajan Singh"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "The earliest written reference about cricket is attributed to one John Derrick. Whilst testifying in a court case, the record has him saying that he 'played creckett' at the Royal Grammar School in Guildford. In what century was this?",
        "correct_answer": "16th Century",
        "incorrect_answers": ["17th Century", "18th Century", "20th Century"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which cricket player was the first player in history to score individual 200 runs in one day international?",
        "correct_answer": "Sachin Tendulkar",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Kapil Dev", "Chris Gayle", "M.S. Dhoni"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "As of 2021, which cricket player has the highest individual runs in one day international?",
        "correct_answer": "Rohit Sharma",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sachin Tendulkar", "M.S. Dhoni", "Chris Gayle"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which cricket player has the highest runs of an Indian player in WODI?",
        "correct_answer": "Deepti Sharma",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Dipshika Kerr",
            "Chamari Atapattu",
            "Harmanpreet Kaur"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who was the wife of Abhimanyu (the son of Arjun) in Mahabharat?",
        "correct_answer": "Uttara",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Draupadi", "Gandhari", "Kunti"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Who was the son of Abhimanyu and Uttara and grandson of Arjun?",
        "correct_answer": "Raja Parikshit",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Raja Prokashit",
            "Raja Pranshit",
            "Raja Abhimanyuputra"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following is not among the 10 names of Arjun?",
        "correct_answer": "Veerna",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Falguna", "Krishna", "Bhivatsa"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who won the War of Kalinga?",
        "correct_answer": "Ashoka",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Kalingars", "Kathara", "Alauddin Khalji"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the name of India's first man-made sattelite?",
        "correct_answer": "Aryabhata",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Astrosat", "GSAT", "TES"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Who among the following was the first man to climb Mount Everest without supplemental oxygen?",
        "correct_answer": "Reinhold Messner",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Junko Tabei", "Phu Dorji", "Duncan Chessell"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "When was Jawaharlal Nehru born?",
        "correct_answer": "14th November, 1889",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Yesterday",
            "14th November, 1887",
            "14th November, 1801"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What do you call it when the computer doesn't respond to an input?",
        "correct_answer": "Hang",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Carash", "Bug", "Output-err"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What is the function of the inbuilt hook in React - 'useState'?",
        "correct_answer": "Add and manage state in components",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Check the state of the network",
            "Use a variable named 'state'",
            "Make a global variable"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "If I am coding in a file with the extension of '.ts', which language am I coding?",
        "correct_answer": "TypeScript",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Transcript", "T-SQL", "TrancScript"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which key would you not be finding on a standard Windows 10 laptop",
        "correct_answer": "Command",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Control", "Alt", "Tab"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Billie Eilish is obsessed with which classic TV show?",
        "correct_answer": "The Office",
        "incorrect_answers": ["The Studio", "Musicize", "American Idol"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Mention the exact number of sonnets written by William Shakespeare?",
        "correct_answer": "Hinduism",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Islam", "Sikhism", "Buddhism"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What would you call a person who doesn't believe in the existence of God?",
        "correct_answer": "Atheists",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Nakutakares", "Bharubhuj", "Athereistic"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Which team won the first ICC T20 World Cup?",
        "correct_answer": "India",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Australia", "Pakistan", "New Zealand"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is a group of islands called?",
        "correct_answer": "Archipelago",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Archepelago", "Indonesia", "Toranto"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following languages can't be used to make the main UI of mobile apps?",
        "correct_answer": "Arduino",
        "incorrect_answers": ["TypeScript", "JavaScript", "Dart"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Movies",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the bollywood film, Dear Zindagi, what did Shah Rukh Khan give an example of when he was explaining Alia Bhatt about choosing life-partiners?",
        "correct_answer": "Buying a chair",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Buying a rose",
            "Buying a table",
            "Buying a card"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Right to Information Act in India came fully into force in ____ ?",
        "correct_answer": "October,2005",
        "incorrect_answers": ["October,2008", "September 2009", "January 2000"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Politics",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Which of the following article constitute the 'Right to Life' in Indian Constitution",
        "correct_answer": "Article 21",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Article 16", "Article 15", "Article 14"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Literature",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who wrote the poem 'If'?",
        "correct_answer": "Rudyard Kipling",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Ruskin Bond",
            "Rabindranath Tagore",
            "J.K. Rowling"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Computers",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Which of the following apps don't have a sending messages feature?",
        "correct_answer": "Mac Notes",
        "incorrect_answers": ["WhatsApp", "Twitter", "Telegram"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Science",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "Choose the odd one out based on the methods of transfer of heat.",
        "correct_answer": "Heatwave",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Conduction", "Radiation", "Convection"]
    },
    {
        "category": "History",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Choose the order of the dynasties who ruled the Delhi Sultanate.",
        "correct_answer": "Mamluk-Khalji-Tughlaq-Sayyid-Lodi",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "Mamluk-Sayyid-Khalji-Lodi-Tughlaq",
            "Khalji-Tughlaq-Mamluk-Sayyid-Lodi",
            "Mamluk-Sayyid-Tughlaq-Khalji-Lodi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "category": "Games",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What was the best selling video game in December 2017?",
        "correct_answer": "Call of Duty: WWII",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Minecraft", "Call of Duty: Zombies", "PubG"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Sports",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "In 2004, which menâ€™s soccer team didnâ€™t give up a single goal to their opponents?",
        "correct_answer": "Argentina",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Brazil", "France", "Croatia"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Mythology",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Who was the wife of Lord Ram?",
        "correct_answer": "Sita",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Sati", "Stai", "Siat"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Maths",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the formula of calculating the volume of a cylinder?",
        "correct_answer": "Ï€r2h",
        "incorrect_answers": ["4/3Ï€r3", "Ï€r2h3", "Ï€r2h9"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "What percentage of river Nile is located in Egypt?",
        "correct_answer": "22%",
        "incorrect_answers": ["100%", "83%", "45%"]
    },
    {
        "category": "Geography",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "What is the oldest city of India?",
        "correct_answer": "Varanasi",
        "incorrect_answers": ["Ayodhya", "Patna", "Madurai"]
    },
    {
        "category": "General",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "What is the full form of the chatting abbreviation - 'IDTS'",
        "correct_answer": "I don't think so",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "I danced thinking so",
            "I don't think such",
            "I don't think sour"
        ]
    }
]
